

ROHIT JAIN

KOLKATA: INDIA: WB 711109 · (983) 123-4170 CERT.ROHIT@GMAIL.COM

Experienced Automation Engineer with demostrated history of working in all phases of Software Testing Life Cycle (STLC), experienced in developing Test Cases, Test Plan and Automation test scripts using Selenium, BDD, Gherkin, SOAPUI with programming experiences in JAVA, C# and Typescript in CI/CD environment. Diversified experience in Automation, Manual testing and Business Analyst role.









EXPERIENCE

TEST ARCHITECT

HCL TECHNOLOGIES

Key member of COE Team for design and development of Automation Framework that cater the need of automating multiple applications.

October 2016 - Present

SDET

FIRST AMERICAN CORP.

Integrated Title and Settlement Transactions system - flagship product and business backbone of the organization supporting over 100+ other Title Products with over 20,000 internal users in over 40+ countries. Have coordinated with the teams for automating 300+ User stories in a span of just 10 months.

August 2013 - October 2016

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN

CMC LIMITED

Decemember 2012 - February 2013

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF TECHOLOGY, WEST BENGAL

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY

Computer Science GPA: 7.58 July 2009 - June 2013

MARIA'S DAY SCHOOL

HIGHER SECONDARY

ISC Board 82.9% April 2008 - March 2009

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES & TOOLS



































WORKFLOW

- ✓ Test Automation, Framework Design
- ✓ Cross Browser Testing & Debugging
- Cross Functional Teams
- ✓ Agile Development & Scrum

INTERESTS

Apart from being a Automation Engineer, I enjoy most of my time being outdoors. In the winter, I am a tennis enthusiaist. During the warmer months, I enjoy travelling to hill stations.

When forced indoors, I follow a number of sci-fi and books on comparative religion, I am an aspiring chef, and I spend a large amount of my free time exploring the latest technology advancements

AWARDS & ACCOLADES

- ▼ FAI Super QA Card
- FAI Momento pat on back appreciation
- ₹ HCL SPOT Award for consistent delivery on 0% post production issues
- PHCL XTRAMILES appreciation for peer to peer support recognition twice